

# HAMZA YOUNAS

Data Entry Specialist

### **PROFILE**

Over 2.5 years experience in successfully performing a number of data entry and clerical tasks. Proven ability to collect and manage information efficiently and accurately. Excellent written and verbal communication skills, strong desire to work hard, and perform well.

#### **SKILLS**

SQL Database
Microsoft Excel
Microsoft Office
Data Science
Data Visualization

#### **CONTACT ME**

+923026902132

hyounas0026@gmail.com

c/o prof.saif ur rehman chak 13/g tehsil chishtian,punjab, pakistan

## **EDUCATION**

THE ISLAMIA UNIVERSITY OF BAHAWALPUR
(Bachelor of Science in Computer Science)
March 2021-Current

**WORK HISTORY** 

DATA ENTRY CLERK AT SUTLEJ PARK LIBRARY

2725+MVQ, Eid Gah Rd, Bahawalnagar November 2021 – July 2022 **DATA SPECIALIST AT DARAZ HOUSE, LAHORE** 

December 2022 - June 2023

COURSES

DATA ANALYSIS WITH PYTHON, COURSERA April 2023 - August 2023 DATA ENTRY COURSE, UDEMY September 2020 - January 2021 WHAT IS DATA SCIENCE?, COURSERA January 2023 - March 2023

> REFERENCE

PROF.HAMMAD SAEED(LIBRARY SUPERVISOR) ham809368@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Prepared documents for data entry Verified, updated and corrected source documents Entered data into designated database and forms Researched and retrieved requested data